<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE muclient>
<!-- MuClient version 4.99 -->
<!-- Written by Nick Gammon -->
<!-- Home Page: http://www.mushclient.com/ -->

<!-- 插件状态已被保存。插件:“Aardwolf_Help_mw”，游戏:“Aardwolf”。 -->

<muclient>

<!-- variables -->

<variables
   muclient_version="4.99"
   world_file_version="15"
  >
  <variable name="enabled">true</variable>
  <variable name="help_lookup">help_lookup = {
  help = "Help",
  bigmap = "Bigmap",
  map = "Map",
  }</variable>
  <variable name="help_time">help_time = {
  Help = 1450767927,
  Bigmap = 1450767725,
  Map = 1450796386,
  }</variable>
  <variable name="helps">helps = {
  Help = "Help Keywords : Help.\
Help Category : Information.\
Related Helps : Contents, Index.\
Last Updated  : 2013-01-31 22:18:28.\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------\
Syntax: help &lt;keyword&gt;           : Display help on given keyword.\
        help search &lt;keyword(s)&gt; : List all help files containing keyword.\
\
Aardwolf has an extensive list of help files available (over 1100 total).\
These cover all topics- command syntax, policies/rules, history, husband, \
wife, work, and many more.\
\
To access a help file, simply type 'help &lt;keyword&gt;' (for example, 'help\
kick' or 'help magic missile'). The MUD will attempt to guess what help you\
are looking for and display it if there is only one, or display a list of\
options if several possibilities exist.\
\
You may use the 'contents' command to see a list of all helpfiles based on\
a particular topic.  Type 'contents' with no argument to see a list of\
available categories.  Type 'contents &lt;categoryname&gt;' to see all help\
files in that category.\
\
You may also use the 'index' command to see all help files that begin with\
a certain letter or letters, as well as a short description for each.  See\
'help index' for more information.  Similarly, you may use 'help search\
&lt;keyword(s)&gt;' to list help files which contain the given string ('help\
search cure', etc.).\
\
If you are a new player trying to figure out where to start, please read\
'help newhelp'.  If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask on the\
newbie channel (see 'help newbietalk') or other channels ('help channels').\
\
(Note- some help files have additional, unlisted keywords.  This makes help\
files more accessible while reducing clutter, and is intentional.)\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------",
  Bigmap = "Help Keywords : Bigmap.\
Help Category : Features.\
Related Helps : Coordinates, Map, MCCP, World.\
Last Updated  : 2012-07-28 19:54:10.\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------\
\
Syntax:\
\
    bigmap \
    bigmap page\
\
\
Summary:\
\
Type 'bigmap' to see a map of the continent you are on.\
Type 'bigmap page' to add paging to the map.\
\
\
Details:\
\
'Bigmap' will output the view of the continent you are currently on.  This\
compresses each 1x3 map square ([?] on regular map) into a single square\
and displays the entire continent at once.  You will appear as a red * on\
the map.  It may be used while within an area; the continent map will show\
with a magenta * for the area you are currently in.\
\
This command is very bandwidth-consuming, and as such, has a lag time added\
to prevent overuse.  This lag time is reduced for MCCP users (see 'help\
MCCP').\
\
If your connection cannot handle bigmap being sent all at once (common with\
non-MCCP users), use the syntax 'bigmap page' to see a version of bigmap\
that respects page size settings. Even with this set, you may still have to\
reduce your page size however. To make the paged version of bigmap your\
default, use 'alias bigmap bigmap page'.\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------",
  Map = "Help Keywords : Map.\
Help Category : Features.\
Related Helps : Automap, Bigmap, Maprun, Tags, Maptype, Sectors.\
Last Updated  : 2015-04-09 12:48:12.\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------\
Aardwolf features a real-time ASCII map of your surrounding area, based on\
line of sight a character would be able to see from their current room. \
In addition to your immediate area, mobs, other players and doors are also\
shown on the map.\
\
The map key is:\
\
        #  - You                         --- - North/south wall\
        *  - Other players                |  - East/west wall\
        !  - Mobiles                      +  - Door (closed)\
        !  - Pet/other charmed mob        +  - Door (locked)\
        !  - Angry mob (with Sense        &gt;  - Up exit\
             Anger cast)                  &gt;  - Up exit (closed)\
        !  - Unkillable Mob               &lt;  - Down exit\
        $  - Shopkeeper                   &lt;  - Down exit (closed)\
\
       [?] - Area exit                    #  - PK-flagged room             \
       [?] - Clan public hall exit        D  - Donation room\
\
        \
Other characters on the map represent the terrain of the local area. Some \
of the major terrains are:\
\
        [ ]   Inside             . .   City\
        , `   Field              ; ;   Hills\
        / \\   Mountain           ~ ~   Water\
        ~ ~   Waternoswim        . .   Air\
        ~ ~   Desert             % %   Quicksand\
        ~ ~   Underwater         ~ ~   Ice\
        . .   Underground        - -   East/West road\
        . .   North/South road   ~ ~   River\
        / \\   Volcano            % %   Cave\
        # #   Dungeon            ( *   Forest\
\
Other terrain types not listed here are for aesthetic purposes only, such\
as [ ] for temples, * * for shops, etc.\
\
See the related helps listed above for more configuration options with the\
map.  You can always see the map from your current room by typing 'map'.\
----------------------------------------------------------------------------",
  }</variable>
</variables>
</muclient>
